A Guide to the Jefferson Cable Videotapes, ca. 1969-1985
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Jefferson Cable Videotapes, ca. 1969-1985
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
11458
This collection consists of ca. 300 video reels: sd; col. & b & w; 1 in.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Stored off-site. Users must request boxes 48 hours in advance of desired use. Neither drop-in nor next-day requests can be fulfilled. For additional information, contact Special Collections.
Scope and Content Information
This collection contains ca. 3000 reel-to-reel videotapes of programs produced by Jefferson Cable, ca. 1969-1985.
Arrangement
The 298 videotapes have been listed in the sequence received and assigned a sequential "Tape #" (column 1). However, it was apparent that the tapes are not in proper sequence by any category.
Note: some containers are marked "H.E." or "Not H.E." That evidently stands for "(NOT) High Energy." Not being program identification, the information is not recorded below.
Note: Boxes / tapes that were labeled with more than one program were given a separate record for each title. But in some instances, tapes may have been re-used without the title of the original program being deleted.
Note: The collection includes one 16mm motion picture of "Chalk Talk" which is filed in the motion picture collection.
Contents List
- UVA shots, Speak Out Song 1971/07/05, Tape #001
  Original Tape #C2-12B
- Young Mr. Lincoln 1971/07/05, Tape #002
  Original Tape #1132
- Young Abe Lincoln 1971/07/05, Tape #003
  Original Tape #1130
- Gulliver's Travels #1 1971/07/06, Tape #004
  Original Tape #1033
- Track the Man Down #1 1971/07/05, Tape #005
  Original Tape #1128
- Women of Pitcairn Island #1 1971/07/08, Tape #006
  Original Tape #1139
- Three Musketeers #1 1971/07/02, Tape #007
  Original Tape #1124
- Three Musketeers #2 1971/07/21, Tape #008
  Original Tape #1125
- Star for a Night #1 1971/07/07, Tape #009
  Original Tape #1137
- Star for a Night #2 1971/07/06, Tape #010
  Original Tape #1138
- Gulliver's Travels #2 1971/07/06, Tape #011
  Original Tape #1034
- Track the Man Down #2 (taped-over?) 1971/07/05, Tape #012 .1
  Original Tape #1129
- Camp Holiday Trails (tape-over?) 1975/06/00, Tape #012 .2
- Women of Pitcairn Island, Tape #013
  Original Tape #1140
- Housing Shortage of 1973, #5 Renovation Program - Cowan Case Study #4 1973, Tape #014.1
- Bruce Cheson Trip, Tape #014.2
- Beaver Hills #2, Tape #015
  Original Tape #S-2001
- Promos Studio Production, Promos, Tape #016
  Original Tape #S-2007
- July 4th, #1, Tape #017
- July 4th ? #2, Tape #018
- July 4th ? #3, Tape #019
- Band Credits IVC 1972/10/05, Tape #020
  Original Tape #H-3010
- Bow Trav. Panama/C1 1971/04/08, Tape #021
  Original Tape #HP-3030
- Promo, Promo 1975 1975, Tape #022
  Original Tape #H-3013
- Tape #023
  Original Tape #H-3014
- 1972/10/05, Tape #024
  Original Tape #H-3020
- Desperados are in Town #2 1971/07/14, Tape #025
  Original Tape #3001
- [Untitled] 1971/11/12, Tape #026
  Original Tape #H-3011
- [Untitled] 1971/11/12, Tape #027
  Original Tape #H-3012
- [Untitled] 1971/09/07, Tape #028
  Original Tape #H-3008
- Chalk Talk dubs, Tape #029
- Promos, Sign-on, Sign-off, National Anthem 1975/01/00, Tape #030
  Original Tape #HP-2034
- Craftshop Chair Caning, #6, Tape #031
  Original Tape #HP-3032
- [Untitled] 1975/10/00 (Updated), Tape #032
  Original Tape #3005
- Hangover Square #2 1971/08/25, Tape #033
  Original Tape #H-3004
- Elizabeth Taylor 1976/09/00, Tape #034
  Original Tape #2006
- Craftshop Chair Caning #1 1972/08/00, Tape #035
  Original Tape #HP-3031
- Community History, Madame Marguerite's 1972/11/30, Tape #036
- [Untitled], Tape #037
- Classroom Capers, Focus Blooper Tape, Tape #038
  Original Tape #C-4
- First Live Newscast WJCC-10 (1970) 1971/12/08, Tape #039
  Original Tape #H-3023
- Blooper dub, Tape #040.1
  Original Tape #HP-3041
- Classroom Capers, Dec. Insert - McGuffey Sign-making Class 1971/09/71, Tape #040.2
  Original Tape #HP-3036
- Classroom Capers, Nov. Insert - Football Player, Tape #041
  Original Tape #C-5
- Tape #042
  Original Tape #H-3000
- 1971/11/10, Tape #043
  Original Tape #H-3016
- 1971/11/10, Tape #044
  Original Tape #H-3018
- M.Japg (?) 1976/12/21, Tape #045
  Original Tape #2009
- 1971/11/15, Tape #046
  Original Tape #H-3006
- Tape #047
  Original Tape #H-2014
- Flag Special, #1 Part 1972/06/00, Tape #048
  Original Tape #HP-3040
- Flag Special, #2 Part 1972/06/00, Tape #049
  Original Tape #HP-2035
- Eways, Tape #050
  Original Tape #R096
- Reaching Out, #6, Tape #051 .1
  Original Tape #H-2010
- Camp Slide, Tape #051 .2
- Realities of Blindness 1974/07/00, Tape #052 .1
  Original Tape #H-1005
- British Virgin Islands 1974/07/00, Tape #052 .2
- Adventures of Casanova #1 1972/02/09, Tape #053 .1
  Original Tape #1398
- Sketchbook at McGuffey 1972/02/09, Tape #053 .2
- Reaching Out, #5, Tape #054
  Original Tape #H-2011
- City Council, #2 Noise / Central City 1974/03/18, Tape #055
  Original Tape #4017
- Tape #056
  Original Tape #H-3007
- City Council, #1 Reel - Interim Downtown Parking 1974/05/06, Tape #057
- Arnold Palmer, Tape #058.1
  Original Tape #2088-216
- George Clifton, Tape #058.2
  Original Tape #2651-283
- NFL, Cowboys / Pitt 1965, Tape #058.3
  Original Tape #0261-3
- Championship Bridge, Tape #058.4
- [Untitled], Tape #059.1
- Madison House Volunteer Services 1974/12/00, Tape #059.2
- Use of Land, NC-870, Tape #060
- Absent Host Jack Jouett's Ride 1974/06/00, Tape #061
- Reaching Out, #2 1971/11/10, Tape #062
  Original Tape #H-2007
- Classroom Capers 1975/12/00, Tape #063
  Original Tape #C-28 (tape missing)
- Hell's Half Acre 1972/02/04, Tape #064 .1
  Original Tape #1084
- I Am Woman Special, Tape #064 .2
- Bright Eyes 1971/06/10, Tape #065
  Original Tape #1057-A
- Tape #066
  Original Tape #H-3009
- City Council, Taxicab (1) Fare Increase (2) Ordinance 1973/12/00, Tape #067.1
- I Am Woman, Tape #067.2
  Original Tape #1171 (playback)
- ACC Wrestling Championship, #1 Set A 1975/03/01, Tape #068
  Original Tape #H-1011
- Environment Intro +5 Hinckley Lundsford 1972/10/00, Tape #069.1
  Original Tape #HP-1085
- Snow Queen 1976/06/00, Tape #069.2
  Original Tape #6-A
- Soccer, UVA / Navy 1976/11/13, Tape #069 .3
- Com.idis ? DAR 1977/02/00, Tape #070
- Congress of Cities #2 T. Turner cont. - Cable Franchise 1980/12/03, Tape #071
- Grapes of Wrath 1972/02/25, Tape #072
  Original Tape #1016
- City Council, Tape #073
  Original Tape #H-1025
- Promos, Tape #074
  Original Tape #H-2013
- Lydia #2 1971/11/11, Tape #075
  Original Tape #4037
- Tape #076
  Original Tape #H-1009
- Housing, Tape #077
- Voices with Nancy Lawson 1977/05/01, Tape #078
- Barry Cooke ?, Tape #079
  Original Tape #H-2004
- Bamboo Saucer 1972/02/29, Tape #080 .1
  Original Tape #1156
- City Council, Mall 1974/01/22, Tape #080 .2
- Congress of Cities, #1 1980/12/02, Tape #081
- Tape #082
  Original Tape #H-1034
- City Council #1 Special Meeting - Mall, etc. 1974/07/08, Tape #083
- Classroom Capers, Upper Elem. Music, Tape #084
  Original Tape #1048 / C-26
- Craftshop Chair Proms & Address 1972/08/00, Tape #085
  Original Tape #HP-3033
- City Council, Cable Public Hearing 1972/08/00, Tape #086
  Original Tape #HP-1069
- City Council, Jefferson Cable Franchise Public Hearing 1974/03/11, Tape #087
- Environment, #7 - Water Filter Plant 1972/10/00, Tape #088
  Original Tape #HP-1087
- Mental Retardation, CAARC Preschool 1975/05/00, Tape #089
- Classroom Capers #1, Tape #090
  Original Tape #1050 / C-11
- City Council, Cable Franchise Public Hearing #3 1975/05/19, Tape #091 .1
  Original Tape #1114
- City Council, Cable Franchise 2nd Reading 1975/06/02, Tape #091 .2
  Original Tape #H-1014
- Fun-A-Thon - promo 1973/02/13, Tape #092 .1
  Original Tape #W-2003
- 1976/10/00, Tape #092 .2
  Original Tape #H-2020
- Update, Tape #093
  Original Tape #1015
- Highlights at Monticello 1976/07/04-05, Tape #094
  Original Tape #1051
- Cable 10 News, Mike Gleason, Mike Lantrop, Rickie Haney 1971, Tape #095
- Ridgeway, Tape #096
  Original Tape #H-1020
- Interview, Astronaut Ed Mitchell 1973/09/00, Tape #097
- Downtown Mall Overview #1 1975/01/00, Tape #098
- Buena Vista VA, Tape #099 .1
  Original Tape #1011
- George Rogers Clark Museum, Tape #099 .2
- Bookshelf Jerry Showalter 1979, Tape #100
  Original Tape #H-1026
- Classroom Capers 1975/03/19, Tape #101
  Original Tape #C-8
- Midmont History, Tape #101 .2
  Original Tape #HP-1095
- Meet the Candidates, James Ford, Tape #102
  Original Tape #C-23 1053
- Speak Out, Mental Health 1971, Tape #103.1
- Bob Sean - King Lindsay Printing 1970/10/15, Tape #103.2
- City Council, Jefferson Cable Franchise Hearing #2 1974/03/11, Tape #104
  Original Tape #VTR#5
- Son of Fury, #1 1972/02/21, Tape #105
  Original Tape #1007
- Charlottesville - Albemarle Vo-Tech 1974/12/10, Tape #106
- Court Square - silent outtakes, Tape #107
  Original Tape #H-3003
- Camp Holiday Trails Tape A, Tape #108
- Albemarle County Historical Museum, Tape #109
  Original Tape #1060
- Nuclear [ -ness] Web of Life 1973/06/18, Tape #110
  Original Tape #1041
- City Council, Jefferson Cable Franchise #3 1974/03/11, Tape #111
  Original Tape #VTR#3
- Your Community Workshop 1974/03/08, Tape #112
- Classroom Capers, Classroom Math 1977/02/00, Tape #113
- Production Collage, Tape #114.1
  Original Tape #HP-1089
- Soap Box Derby excerpts, Tape #114.2
- Environment, #3 Air Pollution #2 1972/10/00, Tape #115.1
  Original Tape #HP-1086
- Environment, #1 ZPG - J. Allen 1972/10/00, Tape #115.2
- City Council, Special Meeting #3 1974/07/08, Tape #116
  Original Tape #1155
- Classroom Capers 1977/03/00, Tape #117
- City Council, Cable Franchise Discussion -Rebuild Changes 1977/05/19, Tape #118
  Original Tape #1114 H-1014
- Plants are like People, Tape #119
  Original Tape #7305-4 7305-5 7305-6
- Soccer, UVA vs Hampton-Sidney #2 1972/03/29, Tape #120
- Martha Jefferson Hospital program, Tape #121
  Original Tape #1074
- "UVA" 1972/07/19, Tape #122
  Original Tape #H-3019
- City Council, School Bus request, Tape #123
  Original Tape #4061
- City Council, #4 Jefferson Cable Franchise Public Hearing 1974/03/11, Tape #124
- Sketchbook, Contest Entry, Tape #125
  Original Tape #1115
- Exploring Talent, Show tape 2, Tape #126
- Let's Play Guitar, Guitar A #10 1972/11/00, Tape #127
  Original Tape #HP-1075
- Football, Little League 1974/11/03, Tape #128
- Classroom Capers, Vet & Gym, Tape #129
  Original Tape #C-2 HP-3034
- Environment, #2 Air Pollution #1 1972/10/00, Tape #130
  Original Tape #HP-2030
- Christmas Special #2, Ray Cary - interviewer, Tape #131
  Original Tape #751
- Cable 10 Programs, Reports 1975/01/00 - 1975/07/00, Tape #132
- Population Growth and American Future 1974/06/00, Tape #133
  Original Tape #1396
- Craftshop Chair Caning, #2, #3, #4, #56 1972/08/00, Tape #134
  Original Tape #HP-1058
- Bow Travel, Peru 1972/07/00, Tape #135
  Original Tape #HP-1053
- [Unittitle] 1975/08/00, Tape #136
  Original Tape #1055
- Fun-A-Thon - opening 1973/02/13, Tape #137
  Original Tape #3021 W-1003
- Soccer, 1st half, Tape #138
  Original Tape #1081
- Bow Travel, Venezuela 1971/11/26, Tape #139
  Original Tape #HP-1052
- [Untitled] 1972/10/27, Tape #140
  Original Tape #HP-3021
- Bow Travel, Colombia 1971/09/13, Tape #141
  Original Tape #HP-1051
- City Council, Press Conference #1 0000/02/25, Tape #142
  Original Tape #4008
- Classroom Capers, April program, Tape #143
  Original Tape #C-10 1046
- Art Therapy Elizabeth Howard 1976/11/00, Tape #144
  Original Tape #1004 update
- Don Anglin Production, Charlottesville-Albemarle Vo-Tech 1974/10/74, Tape #145
  Original Tape #4009
- City Council Work Session, School Transit 1974/02/11, Tape #146
  Original Tape #1073
- City Council Public Hearing, City and School Budgets 1975/03/31, Tape #147
  Original Tape #1105
- Classroom Capers, McGuffey School, Tape #148.1
  Original Tape #C-21
- Wrestling, CHS vs Blue Ridge #2, Tape #148.2
- Adventures of Casanova, #2 1972/02/09, Tape #149
  Original Tape #1399 B
- Atomic Energy Commission, Atoms in Agriculture 1973/07/03, Tape #150
  Original Tape #1065
- St. with No Name #1 1971/11/15, Tape #151
  Original Tape #4044
- Shenandoah Shenanigans, Bridgewater Lawn Party 1975/07/09, Tape #152.1
- Kidnapped #2 1971/12/08, Tape #152.2
  Original Tape #1323
- Meet your Congressman, J. Kenneth Robinson 1974/04/19, Tape #153
- Church, Hinton Avenue Methodist 1972, Tape #154
- Meet the Candidates, City Council 0000/04/30, Tape #155
  Original Tape #1113
- Community Careers, #2 (1) Painter (2) Wrecker 1973/10/24, Tape #156
  Original Tape #1068
- Let's Play Guitar, Guitar A #13, Tape #157
  Original Tape #HP-1077
- Reaching Out, #4 - UVA Tour, Tape #158.1
  Original Tape #H-2008
- Sketchbook, Landscape Artist 1975/01/00, Tape #158.2
- Logos I & II 1975/09/15, Tape #159
  Original Tape #1022
- Basketball, UVA vs ? Reel 1, Tape #160
- Gas Shortage, Tape #161
  Original Tape #1045
- Karate Classroom, #7 and #8 1972/09/00, Tape #162
  Original Tape #HP-1063
- Heidi #1 1972/02/24, Tape #163
  Original Tape #1013
- Soap Box #2, Tape #164
  Original Tape #C-1 1056
- City Council, Gas Shortage - Recomm. 1974/05/13, Tape #165
  Original Tape #1395
- Camp Holiday Trails, Summer Adventure 1975/05/00, Tape #166
- Sketchbook, Christmas 1975/12/22, Tape #167
  Original Tape #C-15
- Soccer, UVA vs. Clemson, 2nd half, Tape #168
- [Untitled], Tape #169
  Original Tape #H-1017
- Promos 1971/11/16, Tape #170
  Original Tape #H-3015
- Atomic Energy Commission, Atoms in Business / Atomic Power Today 1973/06/18, Tape #171
  Original Tape #1040
- City Planning Commission, Press Conference 1974/07/22, Tape #172
  Original Tape #1397 VTR-2
- Son of Fury #2 1972/02/21, Tape #173
  Original Tape #1008
- [Untitled], Tape #174
  Original Tape #1042
- Classroom Capers, #1 School Bus Hearing, Tape #175
  Original Tape #C-29
- Charlottesville Community Development, Interviews for Meeting 1974/10/29, Tape #176
- Jane Eyre #3 1971/07/21, Tape #177
  Original Tape #1153
- City Council, Interim Downtown Parking #2 1974/05/06, Tape #178
  Original Tape #1110
- Tape #179
  Original Tape #H-1039
- To the Shores of Tripoli #1 1971/06/12, Tape #180
  Original Tape #1063
- [Untitled], Tape #181
  Original Tape #1041 C-22
- City Council, TV Cable Hearing 1975/05/19, Tape #182.1
  Original Tape #1328
- City Council, Final Action re: resolution re: sale of Jefferson Cable 1975/06/25, Tape #182.2
- Congress of Cities Part I (Ted Turner) 1980/12/03, Tape #183
  Original Tape #H-1024
- Showdown at Boot Hill 1972/02/17, Tape #184.1
  Original Tape #4004
- Frank Capra, interviewed by Ray Berry 1973/01/20, Tape #184.2
- Camera at the Complex 1975/06/00, Tape #185
- Ice Hockey, UVA 1972/09/08, Tape #186
  Original Tape #H-2000
- Outlaw, Tape #187 .1
  Original Tape #H-1030
- UVA Lawn Project #2 1975/05/00, Tape #187 .2
- Outlaw #2, Tape #188.1
  Original Tape #H-1008
- UVA Lawn Project #2 1975/05/00, Tape #188.2
- Basketball, Little League 1975/03/14, Tape #189
  Original Tape #H-1027
- UVA Lawn Project, H-1022 1975/07/00, Tape #190
- [Untitled], Tape #191
  Original Tape #H-1023
- Wrestling, CHS vs BR part 1 1974/12/06, Tape #192
- It's a Wonderful Life #3 1971/10/12, Tape #193
  Original Tape #4006
- Greenwood House location 1971/03/17, Tape #194
- City Council, Special Meeting 1974/07/08, Tape #195
  Original Tape #S-1002
- Camp Holiday Trails(dub effort) 1975/03/00, Tape #196
  Original Tape #1122
- Hell's Half Acre #1 1972/02/04, Tape #197.1
  Original Tape #1083
- WQRK, Lawn Party, Tape #197.2
- City Council, Rebuild Approval 1977/06/06, Tape #198
  Original Tape #H-1036
- [Untitled], Tape #199
  Original Tape #H-1006
- 1972/10/31, Tape #200
  Original Tape #H-1028
- City Council, Public Hearing re: City & School Budgets #3 1975/03/31, Tape #201
- City Council, Central City #3 1974/03/18, Tape #202
  Original Tape #1109 VTR-3
- City Council, Budget Special #2 1972/03/25, Tape #203
  Original Tape #HP-1068
- City Council 1974/01/00, Tape #204
  Original Tape #1018
- City Manager's Press Conference 1974/03/25, Tape #205
  Original Tape #1112
- Soccer, 2nd half, Tape #206.1
  Original Tape #1078
- Channel 3 video test 1975/12/10, Tape #206 .2
- Brookhaven, Tape #207.1
  Original Tape #1038
- Desalting Sea, Tape #207.2
- Pottery, Tape #207.3
- Cancer Films, Tape #208
- City Council, Noise Ordinances #1 1974/03/18, Tape #209
  Original Tape #4106 VTR-3
- Atomic Energy Co Atomic Energy Commission, No Turning Back, Tape #210.1
- Atomic Energy Commission, Warm Coat, Tape #210.2
- Atomic Energy Commission, No Greater Challenge, Tape #210.3
- Atomic Energy Commission, Man and Radiation, Tape #211.1
  Original Tape #1103
- Atomic Energy Commission, Today Tomorrow Begins, Tape #211.2
- City Council, TV Cable Franchise - First Reading 1980/01/22, Tape #212.1
  Original Tape #H-1002
- City Council, TV Cable Public Hearing 1980/02/04, Tape #212.2
- City Council 1979/08/21, Tape #213
  Original Tape #H-1000
- Increase to County & Apartment, Tape #214.1
- Basketball, UVA Orange & Blue game 1974/11/22, Tape #214.2
- In Search of Ancient Astronauts 1973/02/13, Tape #215
  Original Tape #H-1237 W-4016
- Soccer, UVA vs Clemson, 1st half, Tape #216
  Original Tape #1092 (better copy)
- [Untitled] 1974/02/14, Tape #217
  Original Tape #H-3024
- Tape #218
  Original Tape #H-2016
- Craftshop, Christmas Cake 1972/08/30, Tape #219
- City Council, Meeting 1974/02/04, Tape #220
  Original Tape #1019
- Classroom Capers 1975/10/00, Tape #221
  Original Tape #1054
- Classroom Capers, Cann... & Robb 1975/04/13, Tape #222
- Annexation, Meet the Press #2, Tape #223
  Original Tape #H-1003
- Community Helpers #1 1)Vepco, 2) Exterminator, 3) Service station 1972/10/31, Tape #224
  Original Tape #1069
- City Council, Public Hearing re: City & School Budgets #2 1975/03/31, Tape #225
  Original Tape #1104
- Let's Play Guitar 1972/11/30, Tape #226.1
- Dogwood Princesses 1984/04/26, Tape #226.2
- Classroom Culture, Chinese Students, Tape #226.3
- Tape #227
  Original Tape #H-2002
- NCTA Contest, 1974 entries 1974/02/15, Tape #228.1
- NCTA Contest, 1975 entries 1975, Tape #228.2
- Sketchbook, Tape #228.3
- Downtown Renewal - Overview, Tape #228.4
- Soccer, UVA vs Clemson, 1st half, Tape #229
  Original Tape #1010
- UVA Lawn Project, H-1007 (take one) 1975/05/00, Tape #230
- Chalk Talk II #2, Tape #231
- Chalk Talk J.C.C., Tape #232
- Sketchbook, UVA Bayly Museum 1974/03/08, Tape #233
- Kodak Film interview with r. Monroe & Mr. Price (dub) 1972/07/00, Tape #234.1
- First Aid Crew promo, Tape #234.2
- Classroom Capers #2 Close 1973/03/00, Tape #235
  Original Tape #1169 C-9
- City Council, Vote on Downtown Renewal, Tape #236
  Original Tape #H-2017
- Classroom Capers, Dec. Capers 1975/06/00, Tape #237
- JOT, Tape #238
  Original Tape #HP-2033
- Municipal Board, Tape #240.1
- Soccer, UVA vs Navy 1976/11/13, Tape #240.2
- Soccer, UVA 1976/10/30, Tape #240.3
- Private Life of Don Juan #2 1971/12/13, Tape #241
  Original Tape #2024
- Wrestling, ACC Championship Tape 8 Set B 1975/03/01, Tape #242
  Original Tape #H-1033
- Camp Holiday Trails, Tape B, Tape #243.1
- Lane High Game Shows, Tape #243.2
- [Untitled] 1977/02/00 update, Tape #244
  Original Tape #2003
- Soccer, UVA 1976/10/30, Tape #245.1
- Victoria S. D'Angelo, Tape #245.2
- Classroom Capers, Tape #246.1
- Community History UVA Rotunda Preserved, Tape #246.2
- Downtown Mall - Overview part 2 1975/01/00, Tape #247
- Recreation Building being torn down, Tape #248
  Original Tape #H-1032
- United Way film 1974, Tape #249
  Original Tape #D-1013
- Church - Park Street 1976, Tape #250.1
  Original Tape #H-1004
- University Perspectives, Bayly Museum, Tape #250.2
- Youth in Crises, Shenandoah Valley Detention Home, Tape #250.3
- City Council 1979/07/02, Tape #251.1
  Original Tape #1043 C-18
- Classroom Capers, Upper Elementary, Tape #251.2
- Weapon, Tape #252.1
- Soccer, UVA vs Hampton Sidney 1973/12/00, Tape #252.2
- Steamboat Round the Bend #1 1972/02/10, Tape #253
  Original Tape #1402
- City Council, Mall Discussion 1974/10/07, Tape #254
- City Council, City Budget Special #1 1972/03/25, Tape #255
- Chalk Talk, Third Series #2 1972, Tape #256
- Wing and a Prayer #2 1972/03/23, Tape #257
  Original Tape #1123
- Community History, Late "70's, Tape #258
  Original Tape #H-1035
- Congress of Cities, Part I 1980/12/02, Tape #259
  Original Tape #H-2005
- Housing IVY STACKS A11-15H, Tape #260
- City Council, Taxi Cab, Tape #261
  Original Tape #4041
- City Council, Housing Shortage - Recommendations #1 1974/05/13, Tape #262
  Original Tape #1394
- Entertainment, Dana Paul 1973/04/12, Tape #263
  Original Tape #H-1317 W-4013
- [Untitled], Tape #264
  Original Tape #3022 C-14
- Nancy O'Brien - new mayor 1976/07/01, Tape #265
  Original Tape #1044
- Wrestling, ACC Championship Tape 7 Set B 1975/03/01, Tape #266
- Focus, Mall OK'd - opening 1971/06/15, Tape #267
  Original Tape #1080
- Softball, Tape #268
  Original Tape #1031
- Community History, Westover, Tape #269
  Original Tape #H-1015
- [Untitled] 1975/11/17, Tape #270
- Tape #271
- Sign-on 1971/12/08, Tape #272
  Original Tape #H-3021
- City School Report - Dr. Ellana (mid-7o's), Tape #273
  Original Tape #H-3002
- Cable 10 Singon/Off 1975/10/00, Tape #274
- Classroom Capers, II, Tape #275.1
  Original Tape #C-12
- Arnold Palmer, Tape #275.2
  Original Tape #2088
- George Clifton, Tape #275.3
  Original Tape #2651
- Blue Grass Music, Williams Sisters #2 1973/12/02, Tape #276
- Blue Grass Music, Williams Sisters #1 1973/12/02, Tape #277
- Dancercise #3, Tape #278
  Original Tape #H-1018
- Clive DuVal news interviews 1970/05/00, Tape #279
- Classroom Capers, Focus promos (1970's), Tape #280
  Original Tape #H-2015
- Housing Show with Kay Peaslee, A 1975, Tape #281
- Albemarle Issues, Gerald Fisher, chairman, Board of Supervisors, Tape #282
  Original Tape #H-1021
- Lawn Party, 1322 (master), Tape #283 .1
- Shenandoah Shenanigans, Tape #283 .2
  Original Tape #1322
- Snake Pit #2, Tape #283 .3
- Classroom Capers 1) Primary, 2) Upper Elementary 1972/12/00, Tape #284
  Original Tape #1057 C-3
- Virginia Cable Convention 1968, Tape #285
- Housing Series, Case #1 Program 2 1973/09/00, Tape #286
- Housing Series, Case #2 Program 3 1973/09/00
- Housing Series, Case #5 Program 6 (UVA housing) 1973/10/00, Tape #288
- Explorer Tape 1974, Tape #289
  Original Tape #1079
- Housing Series, Prologue Program 1973/09/00, Tape #290
- Classroom Capers, Greenbriar Bike Safety Program, Tape #291
  Original Tape #C-27
- Sketchbook, UVA Bayly Museum SP 1974/09/00, Tape #292
- Housing, Tape #293 .1
  Original Tape #H-1013
- Classroom Capers, Tape #293 .2
- Camera One 1979/11/09, Tape #293 .3
- University Perspectives 1) Honor Committee, 2) Nurse Practitioners, Tape #293 .4
- Albemarle Playhouse Those Follies (local theatre) 1972/04/00, Tape #294
  Original Tape #H-1059
- Halloween Special 1972/10/31, Tape #295.1
- Barney Cooke / Blackey, Tape #295.2
- Classroom Capers, Contest: 1) Puppetry, 2) Tommy Tooth Special 1974/02/00, Tape #296
  Original Tape #C-19
- Housing Series: Epilogue (Program 7) produced by Kay Peaslee 1973/10/00, Tape #297
- Politics & Legislation, Tape #298